{
  "easy": [
    {
      "question": "what does 'Apfel' mean in english",
      "answer": "apple"
    },
    {
      "question": "write 'walk' in simple past",
      "answer": "walked"
    },
    {
      "question": "what does 'mein Name ist' mean in english",
      "answer": "my name is"
    },
    {
      "question": "what means 'machen' in english",
      "answer": "make"
    },
    {
      "question": "what means 'sein' in english",
      "answer": "be"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of bear",
      "answer": "bore"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of bend",
      "answer": "bent"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of bind",
      "answer": "bound"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of blow",
      "answer": "blew"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of bring",
      "answer": "brought"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of buy",
      "answer": "bought"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of catch",
      "answer": "cought"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of creept",
      "answer": "crept"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of crow",
      "answer": "crowed"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of cut",
      "answer": "cut"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of drink",
      "answer": "drank"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of drive",
      "answer": "drove"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of draw",
      "answer": "drew"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of eat",
      "answer": "ate"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of deal",
      "answer": "dealt"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of feel",
      "answer": "felt"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of fling",
      "answer": "flung"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of fight",
      "answer": "fought"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of forget",
      "answer": "forgot"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of get",
      "answer": "got"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of give",
      "answer": "gave"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of gnaw",
      "answer": "gnawed"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of go",
      "answer": "went"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of grind",
      "answer": "ground"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of grow",
      "answer": "grew"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of hang",
      "answer": "hung"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of hold",
      "answer": "held"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of keep",
      "answer": "kept"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of know",
      "answer": "knew"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of lead",
      "answer": "led"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of leave",
      "answer": "left"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of let",
      "answer": "let"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of lie",
      "answer": "lay"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of lose",
      "answer": "lost"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of make",
      "answer": "made"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of mean",
      "answer": "meant"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of meet",
      "answer": "met"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of melt",
      "answer": "melted"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of mow",
      "answer": "mowed"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of pay",
      "answer": "paied"
    },
    {
      "question": "what's the simple past of ride",
      "answer": "rode"
    }
  ],
  "medium": [
    {
      "question":"what does \"to cover\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["beenden","bedecken","befinden"]
      "right":1
      
    }
    ,
    {
      "question":"what does \"guilty\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["schuldig","mutig","ehrenhaft"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,
      {
      "question":"what does \"goal\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["Ziel","Schatten","Niederlage"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"application\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["Bewerber/in","Bewerbung","Leistung"]
      "right":1
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"award\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["Leistung","Gewinner","Preis"]
      "right":2
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"recently\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["neu","kürzlich","erfolgreich"]
      "right":1
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"successful\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["erfolgreich","schriftlich","wertvoll"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"candidate\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["Vorstellungsgespräch","Grund","Bewerber/in"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"basic\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["schriftlich","mündlich","grundlegend"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"reference\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["Erfindung","Erfahrung","Empfehlung"]
      "right":2
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"grateful\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["untreu","großartig","dankbar"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"opportunity\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["Gemeinde","Gelegenheit","Willenskraft"]
      "right":1 
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,  {
      "question":"what does \"...\" mean in german?"
      "answer":["0","1","2"]
      "right":0
      
    }
    ,
  ]
}
